Narrator: 1
Speaker 1: Can I help you?
Speaker 2: Yes, I’d like a latte, please.
Speaker 1: Regular or large?
Speaker 2: Large, please.
Speaker 1: To have here or take away?
Speaker 2: To have here.
Speaker 1: That’s three pounds forty, please.
Narrator: 2
Speaker 1: Where are my car keys?
I can’t find them anywhere.
Speaker 2: I don’t know. In your jacket pocket?
Speaker 1: No, they aren’t there.
Speaker 2: How about on the hall table?
Speaker 1: No.
Speaker 2: Are you sure you don’t have them?
Speaker 1: Absolutely sure.
Speaker 2: Look in the living room.
Narrator: 3
Speaker 1: Oh no, it’s twenty minutes late.
Speaker 2: Is there a waiting room somewhere?
It’s really cold here on the platform.
Speaker 1: No, I don’t think so.
Speaker 2: What’s the time now?
Speaker 1: Six fifteen. We can take the six twenty, but it’s a slow train.
Speaker 2: No, let’s wait, then.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: OK, come on everyone, out here.
Right, stand together under the tree. OK!
Are you ready? Carole, I can’t see you.
Can you stand next to Jim?
OK, ready?
Say cheese!
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: …So, Mr Bartlett. Do you have any questions you’d like to ask?
Speaker 2: Er, yes. On the website it says the hours are from ten to six.
What about the weekends?
Speaker 1: The hours are ten to six at the weekends too,
but you get paid overtime on Sundays.
Saturday counts as a normal day.
But if you work on a Saturday, you have a weekday free.
The contract says clearly five days a week, with possibilities of overtime.
Speaker 2: Oh, right.